hostdeal.com 2006-03-14

# Privacy Statement - Grand Rapids,hosting,managed server,server colocation,*affordablehost

Affordablehost Privacy Policy

Effective 5/5/2005

**Our Commitment To Privacy:**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). 

**The Information We Collect:**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Affordablehost website. We collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and second, to provide you with the best possible service. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive software. Some of the types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

• Name  
• Address  
• Email address  
• Phone number  
• Credit Card information

**The Way We Use Information:**  
The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order or to the extent that membership organizations whose members use our services may be provided with this information to allow them to monitor satisfaction with the services we provide. Affordablehost reserves the right to reveal this information pursuant to a valid subpoena or court order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive for tech support, customer service, email updates and to send registered users their unlock codes. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

We may use technology to track the patterns of behavior of visitors to our site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you through our billing interface. If you find any inaccuracies you can delete or correct it promptly. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

All online credit card transactions are performed only on secure servers through a secure SSL connection. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**Third-Party Websites:**  
This website may provide links to third-party websites. Any such links are provided solely as a convenience to you. Affordablehost has no control over these websites or their content and does not assume any responsibility or liability for these websites. Affordablehost does not endorse or make any representations about these websites, or any information, materials, or products found thereon. If you access any of the third-party websites linked on this Web site, you do so at your own risk. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**   
At any time, you may later review or update the personal information we have collected online from you by accessing your billing profile. If you have problems accessing this tool send us a support request to [support@affordablehost.com](mailto:support@affordablehost.com)

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us:**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [support@affordablehost.com](mailto:support@affordablehost.com).
